[Music: ‘Gyunwoo and Fairy’ theme song]
[light music]
(Homeroom teacher) Is the bathroom a water park?
Why are you playing in the water there, huh?
(Seongah) I’m sorry
(Jinwoong) We didn’t play in the water?
(Homeroom teacher) Ah
Is it fire play, not water play?
Because you smoked?
Just really, really, shit
One week of volunteer work on campus for everyone
- (Male Student 1) Teacher!
- (Jinwoong) Yes?
- (Homeroom teacher) Why, two weeks, two weeks?
- (Male Student 2) Ah, teacher!
(Male Student 1) I did it last week too?
(Male Student 2) Please take a look!
(Male student 1) Don’t write it down!
Park Seong-ah, really.
(Male student 2) Park Seong-ah...
[Screaming sound]
(Gyeonwoo) Don’t come, tell me there
[lively music]
I think there was some misunderstanding
The one that was secretly hiding in the men's bathroom?
Or did you fire a water cannon at me?
Which of the two is a misunderstanding?
Both must be mistaken
Actually, there was something there.
I was trying to get rid of it...
What was there?
Water ear...
bug, cockroach
Uh, there was a cockroach there.
(Seongah) I really hate bugs.
So I saw him by chance
I thought I should catch it
After a desperate struggle...
Um, stop
But
I don't really like cockroaches
(Gyeonwoo) At least he doesn’t shoot water at me.
They don’t even let me clean the bees.
If you consider only the harmful ones
It seems like you are much more harmful than him?
[Soft music]
So, always stay there, don't come close.
- No...
- (Gyeonwoo) Don’t come.
[sigh]
[lively music]
(Seongah) But it’s okay because I survived.
my first
[Dog barking]
buy
Lang
[Dog barking]
(Jinwoong) Oh, because of Park Seong-ah
What do you mean by bee cleaning?
[dog growling sound]
[dark music]
[Dog barking]
[The dog growls and barks]
[Sound of snapping fingers]
[Dog barking]
[Seongah’s urgent groan]
Are you crazy because you want to start a fire?
[Burning sound]
[Meaningful sound effects]
(Seongah) Who knows how to be scared?
Are you a little scared?
Shut up
I'm not scared
(Jinwoong) Even like this?
[Sound of face burning]
[Seongah’s surprised gasp]
[humorous music]
(Seongah) Jinwoong... there were lice?
Oh, hello?
[Jinwoong’s snort]
Do you want to do that with me now?
Hey, what I just said
I didn't do it to you, I...
(Seongah) Ah, that...
[dog whining]
I did it to you...
Hey
(Jinwoong) Are you too picky?
You're just being silly, huh?
I'm a fan of women too
(Seongah) You don’t have to fuss.
What is winnowing, eating?
Do you know why I came here?
I came here to do all the cleaning.
I'm going to do everything for you three.
Do you know my heart?
Jinwoong Kim
Do you know my deep heart?
(Jinwoong) Uh...
I didn't know
So!
Without even knowing
Go, go quickly, go
[Screaming sound]
go away
(Jinwoong) Hey, you do this alone...
- Good luck!
- (Seongah) Yes!
- (Male student 1) Clean up.
- Don't worry.
- (Male Student 2) Thank you
- (Jinwoong) Hey, it’s a mess?
(Male Student 1) Hey, let’s go to the cafeteria.
[Seongah’s sigh]
I was so scared, I thought it was true
(Male Student 1) I should eat sausage with ramen.
[Dog barking]
Yoo-hoo, let’s go quickly, let’s go quickly, Yoo-hoo!
Lucky?
[Dog barking]
I helped you because you thought it was cute.
(Seongah) Oh
He's a really strange kid
[Calm music]
[dark music]
[Burning sound]
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
This water demon bastard
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
Oh, oh
[light music]
[Cute sound effect]
(General Dongcheon) Ugh
Ah, it's warm
I think I'll buy it now
(Sungah) Even though I became a cockroach
But I saved it
[General Dongcheon clicking his tongue]
Does bad luck come only once?
(General Dongcheon) All three and seven days
It's bad luck that comes at any time.
Moreover, if you are the one who enters the temple upside down,
He's weaker than a sunfish
The guy who already has the ticket to the underworld in his hand
With what I once saved
Fuss, fuss, fuss
Are you an amateur?
(Seongah) Ugh
Just tell me I did a good job, well done
Have what you can
(General Dongcheon) Erai
So what are your future plans?
I don't know
(Seongah) Write 10 chapters at once
No talisman now
Oh, the water spirit was strong, really.
[Seongah clears her throat]
[General Dongcheon clicking his tongue]
(General Dongcheon) Without hesitation
Don't just jump in
Prepare your defenses again carefully
(Seongah) Huh?
Did you make it yourself?
Are you going to give it to me?
A new daughter who doesn't listen to anything I say or do.
What's pretty?
(General Dongcheon) Oh, I ordered it from a person who listens well.
I received it
you also know
[Sharp sound effect]
[Humorous music] (Kkotdoryeong) I...
This is why I won't use the talisman
That's it, I
[Growling sound effect]
(Seongah) Mother
Just stay still
[Sound effect of walking clattering]
[Seongah’s groans of exertion]
(General Dongcheon) Oh my!
(Seongah) Mom, I love you
(General Dongcheon) Oh my, this grown up thing is disgusting.
(Sungah) [Playing cutely] I love you, completely
[General Dongcheon’s embarrassed groan]
[General Dongcheon’s happy laughter]
[Sungah’s cute voice]
[General Dongcheon and Seongah’s laughter]
Thank you
[General Dongcheon’s happy laughter]
Do you think I wrote it obediently?
[snort]
Try it sometime
[The sound of the flower girl breathing in pain]
[Screaming sound]
[Music: ‘Gyeonwoo and Fairy’ OST]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Seongah) It’s because I swept it all up.
So will it work?
Look carefully
[Jiho’s mouth blowing]
[Jiho’s surprised exclamation]
Huh?
- [Music: ‘Gyeonwoo and Fairy’ OST]
- (Jiho) Ah... - (Male Student 3) Are you okay?
(Jiho) Hey, it’s okay
Talk about it
(Male student 3) Fighting
Cheer up, uh, fighting
Ah, awesome
(Seongah) Hey, it’s awesome
(Homeroom teacher) Now, take a seat quickly.
- (Seongah) IC
- (Homeroom teacher) Hurry up and sit down.
Now, Gyeonwoo’s grandmother
He brought snacks as a favor.
[Students cheering]
Okay, applause.
Now
- Boongyi, is it delicious?
- (Example) Yes
Teacher, can you buy me a drink?
(Homeroom teacher) I have to go now too
(Jiho) Hey, the rice cake is really delicious
[Seongah’s sigh]
[School bell rings]
(Homeroom teacher) Now, take care of the trash and go.
(together) Yes!
[Sungah’s heavy breathing]
- (Jiho) Whoa!
- (Seongah) Ah!
I'm surprised
(Jiho) What are you doing?
(Seongah) Hey, I thought you were Gyeonwoo.
What should I do?
I can't do this
Ah, you idiot
(Jiho) Give me the amulet and phone
- (Sungah) Thank you
- (Oksun) Hey, students.
Isn’t that our Gyeonwoo phone?
Because I drew the forsythia flower
(Seongah) Ah...
(Jiho) Ah...
[Awkward laughter]
[Gyeonwoo’s sigh]
Rice cake has been around since ancient times.
a time-honored bribe
[The chief priest's exclamation]
It's somehow suspicious
Su, are you suspicious?
[The sound of the master monk smelling]
It smells bad
Guri-guri, Guri-guri
[Sound of chair being pushed]
(Example) Guriguri?
Are you suspicious?
[light music]
Write, where are our transfer students?
- Shall we start by looking for Byulstar’s ID?
- (Example) Yes
(Joo Seung) Huh?
Next generation national team?
Why is that guy here?
(Oksun) I’m thankful that you found my cell phone.
Even to take you to the beach?
(Jiho) Ayu
We're on our way anyway, right?
[Oksun’s moans of pain]
(Seongah) Huh?
Are you okay?
(Oksun) Yes...
Phew, it's okay
- (Gyeonwoo) Grandma! grandmother, grandmother
- (Oksoon) Oh
(Gyeonwoo) Oh, I’m sorry, I
- I lost my phone.
- (Oksoon) Oh
These guys found this for me
[Oksun’s heavy sigh]
(Gyeonwoo) What’s different about this?
Did you touch it?
(Jiho) Your phone?
Why us?
(Seongah) Yes, yes!
Do we look like such ignorant kids?
Chi
(Jiho) You might look like that
(Seongah) Hey
[Oksun’s light smile]
Wow, I already have a friend.
no
not friends
I want to be friends
(Seongah) Grandmother
I want to become friends with that guy.
[Calm music]
(Gyeonwoo) Ordinary people
I don't go next to unhappy people
Even though we do jeokseon, we don't eat together.
Let's eat together
Let’s eat and become friends, let’s
(Hyeri) What is it? Was he a transfer student archery player?
- (Female Student 1) Gold medal?
- (Female Student 2) Awesome
(Joo Seung) Graduated from Junghyeon High School
Just enter the competition
Promising archery player who won a gold medal
Why is he like that?
Did he transfer to our school?
To the last ranked school in the country
He must have been scouted.
- (Female Student 2) Yes
- (Female Student 1) Yes
(Juseung) Hmm, is that really true?
Sharara
(Example) This guy is an arsonist.
He was cut off for setting fire to his accommodation.
[Hyeri’s surprised gasp]
(Female Student 1) Are you crazy?
- how is it?
- (Female Student 3) Crazy
Is it worth turning on the radar?
(Jiho) I want to become friends, so what?
Want me to cook a home-cooked meal?
Shameless? Running away from home out of conscience?
Hey, and a cell phone
You didn't really find it for me.
It's noisy
(Seongah) I have thoughts on everything.
(Coach Yang) Everyone is going home, but I’m the only one
Huh?
ah!
Is it you?
Oh, right?
how is it?
good body friend
Are you still thinking about archery?
(Jiho) Why are you doing this to me?
Come to your senses, please!
(Coach Yang) No.
You have to come to your senses
[Calm music]
you have this body
Oh, this
Hey, you can't just leave this like this.
(Jiho) I’m just going to leave it alone.
- (Coach Yang) It's a national loss.
- (Jiho) It’s not.
(Coach Yang) You...
[Sound of door opening]
(Seongah) Gyeonwoo’s bad luck is so strong
One talisman can’t stop it
The talisman is
The more you install, the better.
The longer you stay, the better.
(Jiho) Oh, so I decided to hide it at home.
- I deliberately made excuses for home-cooked meals.
- (Seongah) Shhh!
You secretly separated Gyeonwoo and Grandma from the house.
In that gap, I went first and
I'll secretly hide the amulet
[Bouncing sound effect]
[Doorbell sounds]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Bubble sound effect]
[lively music]
Excuse me
(Seongah) Excuse me?
Please excuse me
[Gyeonwoo’s light sigh]
Excuse me
(Gyeonwoo) Hey
sit here
(Seongah) Yes
Thanks, that...
But where is your room?
why?
Oh, I'm just curious.
(Gyeonwoo) Don’t be curious
Until grandma comes home from shopping
Stay still
Why, I want to take a look
(Gyeonwoo) Oh, don’t move.
[Freezing sound effect]
sit
[creaking sound effect]
sit down
Only on cushions
[Freezing sound effect]
[Oksun’s sigh]
- Me, grandma.
- (Oksoon) Huh?
I'm sorry.
I'm actually vegan
(Jiho) Vegetarian
I can't eat meat
Oh my, really?
- Yes
- (Oksoon) Uh...
So why don’t you go out?
[Oksun’s light smile]
[lively music]
[Sparkling sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
[Sound of grabbing doorknob]
(Gyeonwoo) What are you doing?
[Swooshing sound effect]
[Humorous sound effects]
You're sitting
on the cushion
[Seongah clears her throat]
Should I kick him out?
[Humorous sound effects]
no
(Gyeonwoo) Drink this.
Did you warm it up?
warm
(Sungah) Um, sweet.
[light music]
You just eat that...
(Gyeonwoo) Give it to me, give it to me
(Seongah) Why, why, why, why, why, why?
Oh, if you don't want to drink it, don't drink it.
- (Seongah) Ah, hey, I hate it! This is my water
- (Gyeonwoo) Let it go, let it go, let it go, let it go, uh, uh?
- Uh, hey, hey.
- (Seongah) It’s mine [Seongah’s surprised gasp]
Huh?
(Gyeonwoo) No...
Why?
why?
You did it first?
[Soft music]
(Gyeonwoo) Huh?
[Sound of door opening]
(Oksoon) Oh my gosh
Are you hungry? I’ll quickly prepare a meal for you.
(Seongah) Hey, I poured it all out because of you.
It's not my fault, don't kick me out
(Jiho) What is it?
What's the mood?
(Sungah) What is the atmosphere?
But why did you buy so much glue?
I became vegan
Huh?
(Oksoon) Oh my, you’re hungry, right?
Oh my, I eat a lot, because there is a lot.
- (Jiho) I will eat well.
- (Seongah) Thank you
- I will eat well.
- (Oksun) Yes
Now
[Seongah’s expectant exclamation]
- Let’s eat quickly.
- (Seongah) Yes
Wow
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
oh
(Oksoon) Eat
(Gyeonwoo) Eat grandma
[Oksun’s light smile]
(Sungah) It’s really delicious!
(Jiho) Grandma, it’s so delicious
(Oksun) [Laughing] Yes, eat a lot.
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
[Humorous sound effects]
[shaking sound effect]
(Jiho) Even if you’re alone, you’re like this
Please raise me well, okay?
Be nice to grandma, man.
[Oksun’s cough]
(Jiho) Ah...
I mean so
(Oksoon) Uh, over there
[Sound of putting down a cup]
This guy's parents
Um, hey, I work overseas.
Leave it to me
I'm busy making money
I can't stop by often
How often do you visit me?
Phone calls come in regularly.
Right, Gyeonwoo?
(Jiho) Ugh, I’m sorry.
Even though I don't know much, for no reason
(Oksun) No, no, it’s okay, it’s okay
Eat it quickly
eat
I'm adopted
It's been a little over 10 years since I haven't seen my biological parents.
Now I live with my adoptive mother.
[Calm music]
(Seongah) My mother is good at using a knife.
Your cooking skills aren't great.
I only know how to make food waste.
This is my first time eating such delicious japchae.
Mmm, delicious
[Seongah’s satisfied moans]
So delicious
Oh my
(Oksun) Eat a lot
Because there are a lot
- Come on, eat a lot.
- (Seongah) Ah, thank you.
Wow
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
thank you
[Seongah’s satisfied moans]
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
It's really delicious
Did you say Seong-ah?
(Oksoon) The kid is really tough, isn’t he?
[Awkward laughter]
I... do I look like that?
(Gyeonwoo) Is it solid or not?
Are you pretending like that?
[Oksoon laughs]
- (Jiho) Let’s talk for a moment.
- (Seongah) Huh?
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Jiho’s sigh]
Why?
(Jiho) Were you adopted?
[light laughter]
The family register is the same.
When I was 8 years old, my mom and dad
I left it at my mother and never came back.
[light laughter]
[sigh]
(Jiho) Oh, you said that...
I do it casually, usually?
Don't you know?
Because it doesn't usually happen
(Sungah) But it’s true that it’s not a big deal.
If it's a big deal
[Calm music]
You just spoke like a grandma.
Lying so obviously that everyone gets caught
Strangely enough, does that make it more noticeable?
This is true
If you have the courage to say it, I will sympathize with you.
If you say it sadly, you look down on it
If you don't like it and keep it a secret
At that time it becomes a real weakness
It's nothing
I shouldn't say anything
nothing happens
[sigh]
(Seongah) Huh?
[lively music]
Huh?
Isn’t this Gyeonwoo’s room?
(Jiho) I think that’s right?
Hey, Pyoho
(Seongah) The last talisman
[Seongah’s happy laughter]
[Humorous sound effects]
(Seongah) Where are you hiding?
Uh, I should put it there.
(Jiho) I will help you
- Oh!
- (Seongah) Uh, huh?
(Gyeonwoo) What is it?
[Humorous sound effects]
(Coach Yang) Ah!
Ah, this turn
That guy from earlier in the day...
It's a cowherd
Bae Gyeonwoo
[Calm music]
(Reporter 1) Now, please look here, Bae Gyeon-woo.
- (Reporter 2) Okay, let’s take a picture.
- (Gyeonwoo) Grandma, come here.
Hey, let's take a picture together
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
Now
[Oksun’s surprised gasp]
[People applauding]
Well done
(Gyeonwoo) Thank you
[Oksun’s happy laughter]
(Reporter 3) One, two, three
[camera shutter sound]
(Jiho) Wow
Do you play archery?
I guess they're really good, they're all gold medals
(Seongah) Is it true?
Can we go cheer next time?
(Gyunwoo) I quit
[Seongah clears her throat]
(Jiho) Ah...
Searching for things in someone else's house
Isn't that rude, huh?
[Seongah’s shy smile]
[light music]
(Gyeonwoo) Why are you doing that?
Are you hurt? Look look
(Seongah) Uh, huh?
No...
I'm not hurt
(Jiho) No, Seonga, you weren’t hurt.
I got hurt, I
Huh? hey!
- Hey
- (Seongah) Hey
(Gyeonwoo) Hey, what’s wrong?
[Seongah’s embarrassed speech]
(Jiho) Ugh...
(Gyeonwoo) Hey! What's wrong, are you okay?
[Sparkling sound effect]
(Jiho) My heart...
My heart was hurt so badly
Oh, it hurts
[Seongah clears his cough lightly]
(Seongah) Sorry, that...
I made a mess, it’s not Pyo Ho’s fault.
I'll organize everything
[cell phone ringing sound]
(Seongah) Hello?
(Aunt) Fairy, where are you?
Please wait for the guests.
[Seongah’s surprised exclamation]
(Seongah) Oh, that’s right
yes, i understand
[Seongah clears her throat]
[Call end sound]
Oh, what should I do?
I have to go to my part-time job
I'll come and sort it out later.
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, I'm late
(Oksun) Ah, hey...
(Seongah) Hello!
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
What's the point of always ending at dawn?
(Jiho) Ah, anyway, that fool, ah
(Oksun) Hey there
Ah, this
Ah, bag, ah, thank you.
(Oksun) Over there
Thank you, Cheonji Fairy
Ah, yes
(Seongah) Yes?
No...
No, how?
(Seongah) I thought you were Gyeonwoo.
(Jiho) Give me the amulet and phone
(Sungah) Thank you
[Seongah sighs in relief]
(Seongah) I will save you
no matter what I do
I will stop all bad luck, grandma grandson?
I will keep you alive for three to seven days.
[Smartwatch ring sound]
More details later, Grandma.
Let's go, let's go, Auntie!
[Oksun’s cough]
[Oksun’s sigh]
(Gyeonwoo) What you saw today
Go to school and gossip or gossip
It doesn't matter
From now on, don't act friendly to me.
Tell that to Park Seong-ah too.
What do you mean, that?
I don't want to be friends with you
(Jiho) Oh, no way
You dropped this?
Hey, I made a mistake, huh?
(Gyeonwoo) Don’t misunderstand anything you want.
There are no hard feelings or anything.
I just hate all people
There is someone worse than Park Seong-ah, this
(Male) Bae Gyeon-woo from Junghyeon High School?
He must have been expelled?
I can't do archery anymore
[Call end sound]
[Sad music]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(H) Gyeonwoo, aren’t you sorry to me?
(Juseung) Gold Medalist
If you pull the bowstring, you’ll win a gold medal
So even though I set the house on fire
I decided to just transfer to a new school and cover it up.
I didn't even report this to the police.
[Exemplary’s trembling breathing]
Wow
(Example) Then, arson is a serious crime.
Is that okay?
(Joo Seung) My words
Why are you transferring a child who is going to go to juvenile detention center?
That too in our class
What should I do, nerd?
i am so scared
(Example) No, nothing, it’s heavy.
(Jiho) What’s so fun about this morning?
[Screaming sound]
[Seongah’s humming]
Seongah Park
Park Seong-ah!
(Seongah) Why?
What is Gyeonwoo not saying?
(Seongah) Yes
don't say anything
I said hello as soon as I met him.
Don't even say hello, don't accept me
[snort]
But does it still make you laugh?
[light laughter]
(Jiho) Ah ugh
[sigh]
(Gyeonwoo) From now on, don’t act like you’re friendly with me.
Tell that to Park Seong-ah too.
He says he doesn't want to be friends with us.
(Jiho) I told you to tell me even after seeing you
Huh?
(Seongah) Why? What is the reason?
(Joo Seung) He’s a transfer student
They say he's an arsonist
Keep your distance, keep your distance
Hey, I don’t know, it’s me.
(Jiho) What a time of storm and fury.
[Seongah’s sigh]
[Burning sound]
[dark music]
(Female Student 4) Oh, that’s right.
Did you hear?
The transfer student in Class 2, that handsome kid.
- (Female Student 5) Yes
- (Female Student 4) He said he was an arsonist.
(Female Student 5) Really?
(Female Student 4) Uh, I started a fire.
They said they were relegated to our school
(Female Student 5) What, I’m so scared.
[Noisy noise]
[Students whispering]
Can I sit here?
(Seongah) Hey, Pyoho
(Jiho) Ah, it sounds delicious.
(Seongah) Hey, it’s delicious
I decided not to be a friend
Do you sympathize with me?
[Jiho’s satisfied moans]
Are you not listening to the rumors?
(Jiho) I heard it
Ah, the meat is delicious
You're not going to eat this?
(Seongah) Hey, you have to eat meat to grow taller!
(Jiho) Even if you’re handsome, you can’t be a murderer?
Did anything else work?
(Sungah) Not even an arsonist
It's just as dangerous
[Calm music]
(Jiho) But?
(Seongah) Next to a person with bad luck,
A big accident happens
All kinds of ghosts are trying to kill him.
Are they all going to rush in?
But I see more than others, right?
I don't believe in rumors
I believe what I see
What did you see?
He's a good lover
(Seongah) Even when all I have to give you is water
The one who warms it up
warmly
[light laughter]
[Sound of door opening]
(Gyeonwoo) I went
(Oksoon) Are you here?
Ooh, it smells good
[Oksun’s laughter]
[Gyunwoo’s surprised groan]
(Gyeonwoo) What did you do so much?
(Oksun) Uh, I wanted to share it with a friend in the neighborhood.
Have you made a friend in the neighborhood already?
He was so nice that we became friends quickly.
[Oksun’s light smile]
I'll be back soon
- Come with me, I'll take you...
- (Oksoon) Oh my, it’s cold, eat it quickly.
(Gyeonwoo) No...
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door closing]
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
[Meaningful music]
(Seongah) Wow
[Seongah’s satisfied moans]
When I saw you that day
(Oksun) He ate Japchae really well.
(Sungah) That’s right, I like it a lot.
[Happy laughter]
Oh my, oh my, oh my, slowly
(Aunt) You can’t go in!
(Gyeonwoo) Oh, I’ll just check for a moment.
[Sound of running footsteps]
(Oksoon) Gyeonwoo
[Gyunwoo’s exasperated breathing]
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
[Seongah clears his cough lightly]
(Seongah) What is it?
[Gyeonwoo’s snort]
Are you going to make me give these things now?
- Oh, no, that...
- (Gyeonwoo) Why?
Isn't it enough to take money and commit fraud?
I do shameless things to the limit, really!
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
(Sungah) Shameless...
Gyeonwoo, it's not like that, I, I...
- Get out of here quickly.
- (Oksun) Oh my, Gyeonwoo.
Oh my, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, uh
Gyeonwoo, listen to me!
That's not it, I...
(Aunt) Fairy, are you okay?
No, he just
Have you become more temperamental?
Oh my
I think our fairy was very surprised.
(Seongah) Aunt
Why is Gyeonwoo like that?
(Aunt) I don’t know.
Grandma is leaving a negative mark on the world.
Who on earth does he resemble?
(Seongah) Oh, no
That's not it
[dark music]
[Sound of burning flames]
I guess I'll die in fire this time
(Aunt) How do you like it?
(Seongah) Ah...
Why do you keep talking about death?
This handsome kid
(Oksoon) Gyeonwoo, I’m sorry.
I'm sorry grandma
Gyeonwoo, I’m sorry for making you upset, oh my.
I'm sorry, Gyeonwoo.
Why are you sorry grandma?
It's all because of me
grandmother
They even made me sacrifice something like that.
I'm bad!
[Gyeonwoo’s trembling breathing]
[Sad music]
I'm not mad at grandma
You're mad at me
There's nothing wrong with grandma
Hey Gyeonwoo
(Oksun) Huh?
[Students talking]
[dark music]
[Meaningful sound effects]
To throw it away?
(Jiho) It’s only half full?
(Gyeonwoo) Just...
While cleaning bees
[Students talking]
I'm not going out
I was getting kicked out.
[eerie music]
[Sound of door opening]
[Sound of door slamming]
[Students talking]
(Seongah) What about Gyeonwoo?
(Jiho) Is that all you have to say as soon as you see it?
(Seongah) Hello, how about Gyeonwoo?
(Jiho) I went to separate recycling.
Did you go to the warehouse?
(Jiho) Oh
[Meaningful sound effects]
[Burning sound]
[cell phone vibrating sound]
This shouldn't be here
(Hyeri) What is that acting?
[dark music]
(Joo Seung) Huh? what?
(Example) Isn’t there a fire?
- (Female Student 6) Where?
- (Female Student 7) Hey
[cell phone vibrating sound]
Huh? Oh, hello?
This is Gyeonwoo’s friend Park Seong-ah.
Gyeonwoo is busy right now...
[Call end sound]
What is it, I hung up
What's important about this?
[Emphasized sound effect]
General Dongcheon
[Thumping sound effect]
Stupid mutt?
[light music]
IC
Flower spirit!
[Sungah’s angry breathing]
[explosion sound]
[Gyunwoo’s scream]
[Gyunwoo’s heavy breathing]
[Sound of burning flames]
[Gyeonwoo’s groan]
[dark music]
[Gyunwoo’s heavy breathing]
[Gyunwoo’s cough]
(Gyeonwoo) Huh?
Please save me!
I'm sorry
[nervous music]
Come to your senses
I'm sorry, Heena.
Because of me...
[Music that heightens tension]
Heena, please
(H) Gyeonwoo, aren’t you sorry to me?
[Gyeonwoo’s crying sound]
i feel sorry for you
[cell phone vibrating sound]
(Gyeonwoo) Yes, I will
[Knocking on door]
(Seongah) Gyeonwoo
[Sound of doorknob shaking] [Urgent music]
Gyeonwoo Bae!
[Sungah’s labored breathing]
Hey Gyeonwoo! Gyeonwoo Bae!
Mistress
[Gyunwoo’s cough]
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
- Gyeonwoo.
- (Gyeonwoo) Go
don't come
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
[Sound of snapping fingers]
[Sound of door slamming]
[Seongah’s groans of exertion]
[Sungah’s labored breathing]
[Nervous music]
(Sungah) Salt won’t last long
Hey Gyeonwoo
go
(Seongah) Gyeonwoo, get out...
[Growling sound of a fire demon]
[Seongah’s startled scream]
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
[Music that heightens tension]
[Sound of glass breaking]
[Seongah’s surprised exclamation]
[The pained exclamation of the fire ghost]
[Sungah’s surprised gasp]
[Sentimental music]
(Seongah) Let’s go out together, together
Why is Gyeonwoo writing a letter of explanation?
Could it be that the fire was started on purpose?
What does that mean?
(Homeroom teacher) So I told you to write a letter of explanation.
That's what you do
to find out what you mean
He's a victim, trapped inside
(Jiho) That’s right, teacher.
Gyeonwoo almost died
What should I do if I have doubts?
(Homeroom teacher) Huh? He wears it
That's the rumor
how did the fire start
I need to understand the situation...
(Seongah) What are the circumstances?
Right here and now without any evidence
Rather than accusing a person of being the culprit,
Are there any other circumstances?
(Homeroom teacher) Park Seong-ah, you!
Have you always been this good at speaking?
I always watch you sleep
Very different today?
- (Seongah) No, teacher.
- (Homeroom teacher) No, don’t argue with me.
Ask him directly
Rumors of an arsonist at my previous school
Tell me what happened
Instead of saying that
He was the one who said he would write a statement of reasons.
Don't keep calling me a bad teacher.
He made the choice, tsk.
- (Seongah) No...
- (Homeroom teacher) Go quickly, I’m busy, go, come on.
[Gyeonwoo’s sigh]
[Sound of door closing]
(Gyeonwoo) Thank you for saving me earlier.
(Seongah) It was just an accident
But why aren't you making any excuses?
Why do you write as you are told?
Then make sure you really...
It's like starting a fire.
What is the proof that I didn't do it?
there is?
I saw it, Pyoho and we both
You guys came to save me
(Gyeonwoo) I was the only one who saw the fire.
(Seongah) Has anyone seen you start a fire?
you said that
Smiling doesn't make bad things better
But does that mean you just stay still?
So can bad things get better?
It's your business, why do you talk about it like it's someone else's business?
(Gyeonwoo) Then what about you?
It's not your job
Why are you acting like this is your business?
Are you itching to help the poor kid?
If you want to help like that
Go to the bathroom and look in the mirror [sorrowful music]
Do you know how pitifully you smile?
So...
If you don't want to feel more pitiful, don't come closer.
What does it matter if you start a fire or not?
That's what it looks like when kids see it that way
(Seong-ah) Mistress, fire demon bastard, quick bastard
It's already running away
(Jiho) He said he was depressed
Do one thing for sure
(Seongah) Ah, something like this
Take the school site
Why do ghosts come out like this?
(Jiho) So are you continuing?
Saving Bae Gyeon-woo?
I have to... I'm not sure.
If you take one step closer
I wish we could just take one step further away
Because I'm just taking ten steps away
I feel so bad
[sigh]
Yes, I went through that hardship.
I heard people tell me to go away
Hey, I didn't tell you to fuck off.
I told you not to come closer
Either that or that
Is it because it's Mr. Bae?
Don't you think the kid is a little ungrateful?
[Seongah’s snort]
[light cough]
[Humorous sound effects]
It's not fun
(Jiho) It’s fun!
- (Coach Yang) Okay, let’s all focus.
- (together) yes
(Coach Yang) Release boldly
- (Archery Club Member 1) Okay.
(Coach Yang) Attach the anchor accurately.
- Shoot the way you shoot, the way you shoot
- (Archery Club Member 2) Yes
[Sound of releasing a bowstring]
(Coach Yang) Eo Yu, Bae Gyeon-woo!
How did your precious body come this far?
I received a call from Coach Jeong.
I don't do archery
Hey, you guy
- I didn't even start with the introduction, but you...
- I don't.
[Sound of grass bugs crying]
[Seongah’s sigh]
[Knocking sound]
There is no court today
We're taking a break today
(Seongah) Ah...
You are not a guest.
Please come in
(Ok-soon) Gyeon-woo doesn’t take good care of you, does he?
(Sungah) It’s not that I don’t give it often.
I don't give it at all
It's like some kind of desert island
Humans are absolutely prohibited from entering
[Sungah’s light smile]
(Oksoon) That’s right
To reach him
It will be very difficult
people
Every time he puts his foot on the ground
I destroyed it without mercy.
Even the centipede's parents
I don't want to contact him
Gyeonwoo was born with bad luck, ever since he was born
[Calm music]
Baby, die
Baby, tell me to die
Incidents and accidents continued.
(Oksun) Oh my, oh my, Gyeonwoo
[Oksun’s crying sound]
[Oksun’s light smile]
Gyeonwoo, are you okay?
To get rid of this terrible misfortune
There is no method that I haven't tried
A shaman who is said to be brave and is looking for a Taoist monk.
There isn't a town I haven't visited all over the country.
It must have been difficult
[Oksun’s light smile]
It's hard
It wasn't difficult at all
How beautifully did the child smile?
(Oksoon) In danger of dying
Even after passing so much
Without any fear
Without feeling intimidated
The haze of forsythia blooms and smiles like the spring sun.
[Oksun’s laughter]
What's all the trouble?
Even if I don't eat, I'm full
[Calm music - continued]
The fairy
You think bad luck kills people, right?
no
Pointing the finger at me, calling me an unlucky bastard
Parents yelling not to play with him
Let's bet on when the child will die
jokes from bad people
Even if I'm alive
If you are treated as dead
People die from then on.
little by little
People
people kill
(Coach Yang) Really... you're not going to do archery?
yes
(Junior) Don’t you know too?
Bae Gyeon-woo Jinx
You know
All of the competitions he participated in ended in major accidents.
(Coach Yang) The bus flips over
Structure falling from the ceiling
A group of kids got food poisoning.
(Junior) Ah, what kind of ghost has possessed me?
There is no end to incidents and accidents around him.
Ah, but as you know,
What is archery?
Isn’t it a mental battle?
If something like that keeps happening, my mentality gets shaken.
We are no longer the number one team
After entering Gyeonwoo
Oh my, my grades were completely ruined.
No, but Bae Gyeon-woo is
I go out every day
Didn't you win a gold medal?
Gyeonwoo did well, Gyeonwoo alone.
that's worse
Ah, so
The kids who turned away out of jealousy
Bae Gyeon-woo is accused of being an arsonist.
(Coach Yang) Your coaches
Are you condoning that?
(Junior) No, Gyeonwoo is the criminal.
the first person to speak
It's Gyeonwoo himself.
- (Coach Yang) Huh?
- (Junior) Ah, it’s all about the fire.
They say it's because of
He wasn't the one who started the fire.
It's true that it's because of you, really.
Now, kids
Bae Gyeon-woo confessed with his mouth.
Why are you asking me to watch it?
The team atmosphere is shit
What do you do when a leader is like this?
You have to make a choice
Should I hold the hand of the cowherd or the hands of the kids?
So I put it, well, Bae Gyeon-woo
(Coach Yang) Write... heh, really.
Hey, first of all, you...
Jesus can't do it
To save those 99
Didn't you abandon one stray sheep?
[Junior sighs]
That's enough, nigga, I can take it
Even if I'm like this
Aren’t you from Children’s Bible School?
I specialize in gathering up lost sheep, I
I'll go
(Junior) Brother, older brother
He's really not easy
What is easy for me?
Why did you do archery?
When did you first start?
Grandma
Did you like archery?
No, look at that, then...
So what's the problem?
Just keep going
(Coach Yang) When you meet, during the competition
Because you won a gold medal
Grandma really likes it
Because I was bullied
I didn't quit archery.
I hate this too
If you keep receiving it, you get used to it.
(Gyeonwoo) And what about me?
I don't need anyone else
All I need is a grandmother
[Calm music]
But
Every time my grandmother comes to watch the game
I see people hate me
All I need to know is
What Grandma Finds
I don't like that
Goodbye, never see you again
[Coach Yang sighs]
(Sheep Coach) Our little lamb friend
So nice and cute
Perfect for archery
(Oksun) Our Gyeonwoo
my poor puppy
I'm sorry even when I look into your eyes
I feel sorry even when I look at your nose and mouth.
I'm sorry even though I held your hand
I'm sorry for everything, I
(Seongah) Grandmother
You say you're sorry for saying I love you
[Calm music - continued]
people in the world
Don't say sorry to Gyeonwoo
(Oksun) Even after doing something I’m sorry about
Don't say sorry
But our Gyeonwoo
Because I couldn't hear you say sorry
I know I did something wrong
I know it's bad
That's why I do it for you
I'm sorry that people in the world didn't say
I... do everything for you.
You're not wrong
you're not bad
Not yet...
I couldn't tell you everything...
[Sentimental music]
Fairy
Our Gyeonhero
I'm really alone now
(Gyeonwoo) Grandmother
Grandma...
[Gyeonwoo’s crying sound]
[Sobbing] Grandmother...
What should I do, grandma?
[Gyeonwoo’s cry]
[Sungah’s heavy breathing]
(Seongah) Ah!
(Oksun) Just once
Just once
Can we please hold Gyeonwoo’s hand?
No time to wake up the child who fell
I left too suddenly
[Sentimental Music-Continued]
[Sungah’s heavy breathing]
(Oksoon) I’m sorry
[Oksun’s sobbing sound]
I...
For asking such a difficult request
(Seongah) Grandmother
Aren't you looking at me too lightly?
About me
There's no such thing as being nice to me just once
If you treat me well once, I'll keep being nice to you.
Even if I change my mind, it won’t change
Just as God does not abandon humans
Just like a mother doesn't abandon her child
continue, continue
It will be sweet
Gyeonwoo...
I'll let you live
[light laughter]
(Seongah) Gyeonwoo
[Sorrowful music]
It’s very dark there, isn’t it?
just in your life
I know that the only star has fallen
I know you're in the dark
[Sungah’s heavy breathing]
Imagining light in the darkness
How difficult is it?
From now on I
I'm coming to you
[Sparkling sound effect]
I'm sorry, I'm like this
Because I’m the country you hate
[Sorrowful music-continued]
(Gyeonwoo) Hey there
No, what are you doing now?
Where are you coming from?
(Seongah) Why?
Am I somewhere I can't come?
Are you saying that now?
I'm going out
Get out, quickly.
(Gyeonwoo) No, can’t you hear me? Get out!
Oh, fuck off!
(Seongah) Still, I will save you
This thing without hair
in a way you hate
Did I come to see you?
Are you here to see your grandmother?
I never leave you alone
[Music: ‘Gyeonwoo and Fairy’ OST]
(H) I heard your grandmother passed away?
Have you finally escaped from me?
(Eldest Dad) Until the last way you go
Dirty like this?
(Gyeonwoo) I’m sorry
Because I am my grandmother’s misfortune
(Seongah) Even if I can’t make you understand
I can protect it
If I have no choice but to be hated, I want to be hated.
I'll do what I can now, just
(General Dongcheon) Until now
It seems like only three people died.
Even ghosts die, there
(Maeng Shaman) This is no longer a person
It's a ghost wearing a human shell.
(Yeomhwa) Hello?